flegoo.com 2017-12-10

# Privacy Policy - Flegoo Classifieds

### Privacy Policy

We have developed the Flegoo free ad posting classified site for US, Australia, India & United Kingdom which is user-friendly and trouble-free as possible. We care about your privacy of our users and are committed to ensuring that your personal information is safe protected. We will NEVER share and sell any of your personal information that we collect during ad posting.

What information do we collect during ad posting on Flegoo?  
In order to create your free account and posting any classified ads for you. We require an e-mail address to verify the account during registration and very occasionally we send you news and updates about our websites.

Apart from what you provide, we gather some automated information every time you visit - information such as your IP address, the browser and OS you are using. This is the general information that web servers collect whenever you visit a website.

If you're particularly worried about this, then there's lots of resources and companies that can help you stay anonymous online.

## Advertising Information

We also use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. Advertising companies may use information (not your personal information) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements related to your interest.

If there is anything about our privacy policy that you are unsure about or need to clarify then please contact us.

Please check back our terms and conditions time to time for any updates.
